Hispanic Women's Network of Texas Records
Nettie Lee Benson Latin American Collection
Hispanic Women's Network of Texas Records
1987-2019
Hispanic Women's Network of Texas
1997-02
48.5 linear feet
Benson Latin American Collection, The University of Texas at Austin
Documents, reports, publications, files, promotional material, and meeting material relating to the Hispanic Women's Network of Texas. Topics include women in business, education, health, government, and philanthropy in Texas.
Administrative History
The Hispanic Women's Network of Texas is a non-profit, state-wide organization formed in 1986 which seeks to address issues unique to the Hispanic population in Texas. The Hispanic Women's Network of Texas (HWNT) works to advance the educational, cultural, social, legal, and economic well-being of all women through a broader awareness of their role in society, business, and family. Members strive to celebrate the positive image and values of the Hispanic culture. Members of the HWNT advocate for Hispanic women in all aspects of life, from supporting Hispanic business women through partnerships with Texas Association of Mexican American Chambers Commerce (TAMACC), providing scholarships to Latina students, and hosting freedom marches. Among its founding women were Martha Hinojosa-Nadler, Lena Guerrero, Amalia Rodriguez-Mendoza, Mary Alice Cisneros, Christine Hernandez, and Lupe Ochoa.
The organization is headquartered in Austin, Texas and currently (as of 2022) has chapters in Austin, Corpus Christi, Dallas, El Paso, Fort Worth, Houston, the Rio Grande Valley, and San Antonio. The HWNT previously had chapters in Denton, Lubbock, and McAllen.
The HWNT has an organization-wide Board of Directors with positions including the State Chair, Treasurer, Education Chair, and State Membership Chair. Local chapters have their own organizational structure, host their own events, and each chapter has a State Representative that sits on the Board of Directors.
The HWNT’s largest event is the annual State Conference, which takes place in a different Texas city each year. The conference includes networking, community building, and career advancement opportunities for Latinas across Texas.
The organization also plans events including annual board retreats; Platícas Poderosas, a lecture series; The Estrella Awards, which honors members of the HWNT that have made an outstanding impact in their communities; and the Latinas in Progress Education Program, which assists Latinas with the transition from high school to higher education.
Scope and Contents Note
This collection was processed in multiple parts. Part 1 includes materials donated before 2005, Part 2 includes materials donated between 2005-2018, and Part 3 includes materials donated between 2019-2021. The first acquisition includes meeting minutes, publications, conference materials, financial and administrative records, correspondence, photographs, and artifacts, 1987-2007. These materials document the founding and activities of the Hispanic Women's Network of Texas (HWNT).
Part 2: Additions
Part 2 Additions is divided into the following series: General and Administrative, Board of Directors, Committees, Conferences and Events, Collected Material, Local Chapters, Audiovisual Material, Scrapbooks, Oversize Material, Textiles, and Memorabilia.
The General and Administrative Series includes materials relating to HWNT as an organization overall. This series consists primarily of executive material, meeting agendas and notes, directories, and newsletters. This series also contains numerous versions of the HWNT standing rules and by-laws.
The Board of Directors series includes material collected by HWNT board members. The material primarily consists of financial materials such as check requests and expense reports as well as Board of Directors meeting minutes and materials from 1993-2014. The majority of this series is the material relating to the Board of Directors meetings which were typically held several times a year throughout Texas.
The Committees series is divided into the various committees constituted by the HWNT. This committees include the communications committee, the membership committee, the education committee, the executive committee, the newsletter committee, the scholarship committee, and the steering committee. The material in this series includes meeting notes, agendas, and correspondence of those committees.
The Conferences and Events series includes conference material from 1989-2014 as well as general events held by HWNT at a state-wide level from 1993-2007. Conference material primarily consists of planning materials, meeting notes, program drafts, exhibitor information, and correspondence relating to the event.
The Collected Material series includes material collected by members of HWNT that was not necessarily created for or by HWNT as an organization. This includes collected publications, invitations, newsletters, certificates, proclamations, decrees, and pamphlets.
The Local Chapters series includes material relating to the following chapters: Austin, Corpus Christi, Dallas, Denton, El Paso, Fort Worth, Houston, Lower Rio Grande Valley, Lubbock, McAllen, and San Antonio. Chapter materials include clippings, correspondence, events, meetings and agendas, newsletters, reports, and several photographs.
The Audiovisual Material series includes unlabeled photographs, floppy disks, and DAT tapes. The floppy disks in this collection contain administrative information and forms.
The Scrapbook series includes scrapbooks made by members of the Austin, Corpus Christi, and Fort Worth Chapters.
The Oversize Materials series includes oversize items such as a banner from the Fort Worth Chapter, posters, proclamations and decrees.
The Textiles series consists of various T-shirts from local chapters along with HWNT buttons and pins. This series also includes HWNT bags that were given at conferences and events.
The Memorabilia series is a collection of trophies, awards, and other items that were given at conferences. Items include paperweights, a koozie, plaques, trophies, and a key to the City of Forth Worth.
Part 3: Additions
The materials in Part 3 of the Hispanic Women’s Network of Texas collection, 1987-2019, were created and received by HWNT members as they held state and local meetings, planned and attended annual conferences, and advocated for Hispanic women in the state of Texas. The materials in this addition to the collection consist of minutes and agendas from quarterly state board meetings, invoices from events, published materials about the Latina experience in Texas and the United States, and statements on political issues.
While there are some materials from the local chapters located throughout the state of Texas (including the Austin chapter), the majority of the materials in Part 3 are those compiled by specific state board members (Guadalupe Morin, Dora Trinidad, Cecilia McKay, and Carla Romero) and consist primarily of materials from state board meetings and annual conference planning. The collection contains materials from the founding of HWNT in 1987 to 2019. The material is consistently spread between these dates, although the late 2000s and early 2010s have the least amount of material.
Access Restrictions
Unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
Donation.
Accession numbers: 1997-02, 1997-03, 1997-05, 2004-46, 2005-24, 2006-11, 2012-04, 2016-18, 2016-46, 2018-09, 2019-15, 2019-16, 2021-01
Additions
Further materials are expected for this collection.
Index Terms
Subjects (Organizations)
Hispanic Women's Network of Texas--Archives
Subjects
Latin American women--Texas; Women--Societies and clubs--Texas--Sources; Mexican American women
Related Material
The Benson Latin American Collection also holds the Hispanic Women's Network of Texas Austin Chapter Newsletter (at call number F 395 S75 H58) and Vision: A Publication of the Hispanic Women's Network of Texas (F 395 S75 V57)
Chicana Research and Learning Center Records
Mexican American Business and Professional Women's Association Records
Box and Folder Inventory
- Part 1: Original Collection
  The material in Part 1 of this collection was donated between 1997-2004.
  - General and Administrative, 1987-1998
    - HWNT Background Information, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Important Documents, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      The Important Documents, in these Folders include such things as by-laws, articles of incorporation, and documents of tax-exempt status. These documents were originally collected into binders by HWNT members to document the history of the organization.
    - Important Documents, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
    - By-laws and Revisions, 1987-1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Master Plan, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Policies, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Proposed Guidelines for Developing Local HWN Chapters, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - HWNT Logo Proposal, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Procedures, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Includes Board of Directors procedures and "English Plus" resolution.
    - Procedures - Robert's Rules of Order, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Procedures - Grievance Form, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Adelante Mujeres, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1987-1990, The First Four Years, Annual Reports, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Certificates of Appreciation, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Articles on HWNT, 1990-1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors, 1987-2003
    - General (Box 2)
      - Board Manual, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Board Manual, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 6-8)
      - Board Book, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Master Plan, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Rosters, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Goals, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors Meetings (Box 3)
      Includes minutes, agendas, handouts, correspondence, and other items related to the meetings of the statewide board.
      - 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
      - 1989 January (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - 1989 May (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - 1989 July (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Conference Call, 1989 September (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - 1989 October (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - 1990 April (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - 1990 July (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - 1990 October (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - 1991 January (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - 1991 April (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - 1991 July (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - 1991 October (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
      - 1992 January (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - 1992 April (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - 1992 July (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - 1992 October (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - 1993 January (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - 1993 April (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - 1993 July (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - 1993 October (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
      - 1994 January (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
      - 1994 April (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - 1994 July (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - 1994 October (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - 1995 January (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - 1995 April (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - 1995 July (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - 1995 July (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - 1995 October (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - 1996 January (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - 1996 April (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - 1996 July (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - 1996 October (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - 1997 January (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - 1997 April (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - 1997 July (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - 1997 October (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - 1998 January (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - 1998 April (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - 1998 October (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - 1999 April (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - 1999 July (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - 1999 October (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - 2000 January (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - 2000 April (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - 2000 July (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - 2000 October (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - 2003 July (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Meeting Attendance, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Regional Updates, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Executive Committee (Box 11)
      - Officer Information Forms, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Office Responsibilities, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Officer Training, 1991-1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Conference Calls, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Conference Calls, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Conference Calls, 1997 January-1997 May (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Conference Calls, 1997 June-1997 December (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Conference Calls, 1998 January-1998 May (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Conference Calls, 1998 June-1998 November (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Chair/Vice-Chair Correspondence (Box 12)
      - Mercado, Maria Luisa, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Hinojosa-Nadler, Martha: (Box 12)
        - 1990 January-1990 August (Box 12, Folder 3)
        - 1990 September-1990 December (Box 12, Folder 4)
        - 1991 January-1991 April (Box 12, Folder 5)
        - 1991 May-1991 June (Box 12, Folder 6)
        - 1991 July-1991 December (Box 13, Folder 1)
        - 1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Escamilla, Linda C.G.: (Box 13)
        - 1989-1992 (Box 13, Folder 3)
        - 1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
        - 1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Garza-Fracchia, Pearl: (Box 13)
        - 1987-1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
        - 1992 April-1993 May (Box 13, Folder 7)
        - 1993 June-1993 December (Box 14, Folder 1)
        - 1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
        - 1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
        - 1996 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Facundo, Irma, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Vice-Chair's Report, 1995 April (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Treasurer and Financial Documents (Box 14)
      - Treasurer's Handbook, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence (Box 14)
        - Rodriguez, Sylvia, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
        - Rodriguez, Sylvia, Tax Exemption, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
        - Munoz Sanchez, Aurora, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 1)
        - Hinojosa-Nadler, Martha, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
        - Ramirez, Sylvia, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
        - Facundo, Irma, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Financial Documents (Box 15)
        - Budget Documents, 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 5)
        - Financial Transactions, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
        - Financial Transactions, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
        - Financial Statements, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
        - Financial Statements, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 9)
        - Financial Statements, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
        - Audit, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
        - Financial Statements, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
        - Financial Statements, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 3)
        - Financial Statements, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
        - Financial Statements, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
        - Tax Documents, 1988-1993 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Articles of Association and Group Exemption, 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
      - Group Exemption, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Other Financial Documents, circa 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Historian (Box 17)
      - Scrapbook, 1987-1990 (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
  - Committees, 1988-2000
    - Communications Committee and Publications (Box 18)
      - Correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - PR/Marketing Plan, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Vision Newsletter: (Box 18)
        - 1988 (Box 18, Folder 3)
        - 1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
        - 1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
        - 1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
        - 1992 (Box 18, Folder 7)
        - 1993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
        - 1994 (Box 18, Folder 9)
        - 1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
        - 1996 (Box 18, Folder 11)
        - 1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
        - 1998-2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - State Membership Directories: (Box 19)
      - 1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - 1991 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - 1992 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - 1994 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - 1995 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - 1996 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - 1998 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Other Publications: (Box 19)
      - Brochure: Celebrating Pride in Our Heritage Through Professional Interaction, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Membership Committee (Box 20)
      - Membership, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Membership, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Membership Drive, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - HWNT File List, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - HWNT File List, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Membership, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Membership Development Training Manual, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Member Data, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Membership Package, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Membership, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Organization, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Business Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Business and Economic Development Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - By-laws Committee, 1988-1992 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Education Committee, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Fund Development Committee, 1991-1996 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Issues Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Culture Subcommittee, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Lobbying, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Meetings, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Redistricting Subcommittee, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Voter Registration (Texas Women Vote Project), 1990 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Nomination Committee, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Service Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Structural Proposal Committee, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Transitions Committee, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Special Committees Responsibilities, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Annual Conferences and Special Events, 1987-2001
    - Annual Conference, Conference Packet, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Annual Conference, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Conference Planning (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Conference Packet, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Annual Conference, Conference Packet, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Annual Conference, 1990 (Box 22)
      - Conference Planning Manual, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Conference Planning, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Conference Packets, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
    - Annual Conference, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Conference Planning, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Conference Packets, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
    - Annual Conference, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Conference Planning, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Conference Packet, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Annual Conference, 1993 (Box 23)
      - Conference Planning, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Conference Packet, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
      - Chair Elect Materials, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Scrapbook/Notebook, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Annual Conference, 1994 (Box 24)
      - Conference Planning, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Conference Packet, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Scrapbook/Notebook, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Annual Conference, 1995 (Box 25)
      - Conference Planning, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
      - Conference Packet, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
      - Scrapbook/Notebook, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Annual Conference, 1996 (Box 25)
      - Conference Planning, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Proclamation by Austin Mayor Bruce Todd, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Scrapbook/Notebook, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Chair Materials, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Annual Conference, 1997 (Box 26)
      - Conference Planning, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Scrapbook/Notebook, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Annual Conference Photographs, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Located in: Audiovisual Materials
    - Annual Conference Program, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Annual Conference Announcement, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Scrapbook/Notebook of Annual Conferences, 1987-1994 (Box 26, Folder 8-9)
    - Annual Membership Meetings: (Box 27)
      - 1992 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - 1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - 1994 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Special Events and Activities (Box 27)
      - 1990 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - 1991 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - 1992 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - 1993 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Diego Rivera Exhibit, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - 1994 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - 1995 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Various, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Collected Materials, 1990-1998
    Materials from other related organizations collected by HWNT.
    - National Network of Hispanic Women, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 12-13)
    - National Roundtable for Hispana Presidents of Volunteer Organizations and Leaders, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
    - Mexican American Women's National Association, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Hispanic 50 By-laws, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Hacemos, Budget, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Various, 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Local Chapters, 1988-2004
    - Austin Chapter, 1988-2004 (Box 29)
      - General and Administrative Records (Box 29)
        - General Chapter Focus, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 1)
        - Brochure, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - City Permit Application, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - Clippings, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - Letterhead, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
        - Media List, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - Member Addresses, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - Membership Lists, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 8)
        - Membership Lists, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 9)
        - Officers, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 10)
        - Officers Orientation Manual, 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 11)
        - Officers Training Manual, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 12)
        - Phone Tree, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 13)
        - Region 8 Training Session Binder, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 14)
        - Reports, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 15)
        - Secretary, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Meetings (Box 30)
        - Membership Meeting Agendas, 1988-1996 (Box 30, Folder 1)
        - Austin Chapter Minutes, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 2)
        - Membership Meeting, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 3)
        - Officers Meeting, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
        - Austin Chapter Minutes, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
        - Executive Committee Meetings Minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 30, Folder 6)
        - Austin Chapter Minutes, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
        - Special Meetings, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
        - Austin Chapter Agenda, Minutes, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 9)
        - Executive Board Meetings, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 10)
        - Executive Officers and Regular Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1993-2000 (Box 30, Folder 11)
        - Membership Meetings, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Newsletter, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Newsletter, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Newsletter, 1993-2003 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Newsletter Printing Bid, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Austin Chapter Events (Box 31)
        - Día de las Madres Breakfast, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 5)
        - Día de las Madres Breakfast, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 6)
        - Día de las Madres Breakfast, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 7)
        - Día de las Madres Breakfast, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 8)
        - Día de las Madres Breakfast, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 9)
        - Día de las Madres Breakfast, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 10)
        - Style Show, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 11)
        - Scholarship Banquet, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 12)
        - Scholarship Banquet, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 13)
        - Scholarship Banquet, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 14)
        - Scholarship Banquet, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 1)
        - Scholarship Banquet, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - Scholarship Banquet, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 3)
        - Events, 2002-2004 (Box 32, Folder 4)
        - Various Events, 1989-2000 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Photographs, circa 2000 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Austin Hispanic Coalition for Fair Redistricting, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 7-11)
      - Various Binders (Box 33)